Zone even from the first time I was on
here and I was like so nervous and like
I didn't know what to say yes absolutely
I would write for the hustle Zone well
I'm going to send you an email it is
very daunting there's a lot of there's
paperwork and all that stuff but we we
are going to do something really big oh
yeah it's uh it's huge okay but it's
huge but I really want to have you
because I think your story is amazing
and I think that also um you know even
if you didn't tell the story tonight you
know I've been watching your stuff um
like I don't really get chance to
comment or go in to everybody's like
videos right because like if I did that
like I'm sure I would be like doing the
hustles on from like a bridge somewhere
right right but the um you know but you
you just you you live such a really good
life you you seem really happy and you
have a lot of fun with your lives you're
dancing you got kids and there just all
these great things so it's it's like you
know folks that's why like this whole
5,000 friend thing like I got 5,000
friends now and they're all
entrepreneurs you got to keep like folks
you got to keep on adding entrepreneurs
because the thing about it is that
you're never going to find an negative
story on your
timeline straight up like every time you
go down unless someone's like blown man
those black lives matter so block and
delete I'm joking
oh go without a little bit of
humor but no
I but I rarely see people being
political it is just it's like LinkedIn
but where all the people are at LinkedIn
I find that LinkedIn is like the place
where people think they're social media
in they're
like and then just put it out there and
nothing happens but Facebook is like a
place where you know we all get to see
each other's lives and we all get to see
each other expand and grow and to do
great things and you are one of those
people that's why I remember your name
now and I'll continue to remember your
name
Jen I'm gonna kick your butt
Ryan
but thank thank you uh Jesse from the
bottom of my heart thank you for sharing
your story tonight and um absolutely um
there is a tradition on the hustle Zone
where I do a call and response and then
you have to wake up the family and
everything everybody in there and you
got to scream it loud and proud but uh
so I'm going to say welcome to the and
then you're going to be like
H we're still doing that yeah I you know
what I I'm putting together a video
where it's going to be like hustle so I
sent it to so I'm just going to let a
few of you guys I know on a Friday night
the hustle zone is usually like it's not
really
on and popping because people actually
have lives while I'm still you know
doing hustle every day um hold on I'm
just going to send this out to
there so how are you folks doing um you
know we've had a um we've had a hell of
a uh uh hustles on week I mean there's a
lot of great things that happened people
learned how to make $10,000 that was
cool
um and we also um we learned how to
build a brand that was cool and um and
the rest of the shows I don't remember
it's been a breeze but you know um thank
you guys all for tuning in um you you
see me wearing this nice uh hustle Zone
shirt a little bit too small for me but
it's okay
um we we would not be here without the
support of you guys so if you don't mind
head over to hustle zone. clo we got
tanks we have everything um and then
we're going to be building out a
clothing line up pretty soon but you
know we're not like clothing clothing
line worthy I mean like we're not that
famous gez uh but we're working on it um
now um I I do want to say that all the
links to the hustle zone is in the
description so if you want to
participate you want to be part of the
group um you know by all means please
please do so we do have the hustle on
magazine coming up um on September 1st
so you know I want to give a big shout
out shout out to um to Jason Daniels to
Mark and Carla elk Hill um Shantel Lee
Anthony mclanahan Ricardo McCrae and um
and Jamie Lynn these are all and now we
have Michael Haynes now he he's uh the
entrepreneur with cereal paly you know
so he's going to be coming onto the team
and you know all of us are going to be
writing some great articles and I'm and
I hopefully my guests want to write on
the hustle Zone as well so we're
definitely going to ask her tonight um
if she would um what else what else can
I say I mean
um the the whole thing about the hustle
zone is that we are trying to make this
into a like we're attempting to make
entrepreneurialism as a culture not just
a lifestyle because not all of us are
rich not all of us are you know all of
some of us are climbing up that ladder
now and um but we still consider
ourselves as entrepreneurs because you
have those those those mean old guys
that come up on here as like you need to
grind grind hustle hustle hustle grind
and hustle hustle and grind and hustle
and grind take action hustle hustle
hustle grind grind grind take action you
know like holy moly like how many times
I got to hear
10x got a 10x yo tedex hustle action
take action and you're not an
entrepreneur if you don't got Rolexes I
got Rolexes look at me H I'm Puff Daddy
you know what I mean like I
don't I'm I'm playing with you guys but
still um yeah it a part of my life is
all about the hustle and grind but you
know we want to expand upon that
wouldn't you all agree um that we need
to expand on the on on the just the
definition of
entrepreneurialism and you know PE like
some people are saying well the hustle
Zone brand is like more so a
masculine brand and it's not I mean
there's you know every time we have
women on the hustle Zone they give a
different perspective like you know it's
all
encompassing you know we we're we're
we're gender neutral here this is not a
I try not to give off that Vibe you know
even though the earlier hustles on I was
screaming and yelling that's why I'm not
I I try going back to looking at those
hustle Zone videos and I cringe because
I'm
like hustle C you know trying to match
Shane to train I can't Mash Shany train
at all so I'm you know not going to do
that um so we who's going to win the the
$1,000 credit um to bowai creative so we
had um I had Susan tally it up so I'm
hoping Susan would send me a message so
by the time um you know so Susan please
send me the message who won uh it was
between Kelby uh Dixon and Mark elkhill
who won the $1,000 credit so please uh
let me
know um
um
now before we get to our guest one more
thing she's like come on let's go
um who is the best entrepreneur okay so
we have um and of course a part of the
hustle zone is the great debate okay so
um I you guys already see on the top of
my screen here um you know there's a
like button and and a heart button
um the like button is for the my mouse
is doing so some funky things right now
there's a there's a like button and
there is a heart button so um today
tonight's great debate
is um who is the best
entrepreneur so Bill Gates so who's the
best entrepreneur is it Bill
Gates or Steve Jab
come on folks so and make sure you guys
like and share like and share like and
share like and share don't you guys like
the new setup kind of it's kind of like
dis I'm just like I'm going to have to
like scoot over when we do the side by
side but I kind of opened up the the
landscape I got a different lens so that
you guys can you guys can see all of
me
joking anyway so who's on tonight let's
check out the comments
so Rob glow he says he's on point Rob
it's nice talking to you today Rob is a
web designer graphic designer um it's St
Louis thing hustle Zone awesome and we
got Chris Ripka take Massive
Action well yeah you got to you know how
many times we got to hear it man [ __ ]
but I guess that's that's what it's all
about on points okay so who else is in
the room and hopefully Susan can come in
and let me know who wins that 100 $1,000
credit take massive imperfect action
okay so folks so tonight we have a
guest um she has a really fun life you
know uh from uh I last year I would call
her what's up Jen Jen Jen because there
was a girl named Jen that was an
entrepreneur I don't know if you guys
know who this this woman was but she was
supposed to be on the hustle Zone and
she didn't end up coming on the hustle
Zone CU I don't think she thought I was
that serious or something um but I would
call I would mix
her her up with Jessie but I know Jesse
because Jesse Jesse is all over my
social media okay she's combing her
hair she's in the
car you know she's talking about
motivation she's doing you know and I
think she Snapchats as well you know she
is just on point and I've been watching
it for the whole year I've been watching
I've been watching um but you know it's
so funny like not even that it's funny
it's just that you know it's it's funny
how all of us we started out somewhere
and you know we've kind of developed
this community of
entrepreneurs um we've all developed
this community and it's just it's
addictive it's like our children are
like dying of hunger in the background
and we're on our lives like you know
what I mean it's like don't worry
I'll I'll feed you later Let's uh let's
get back on these lives but no but it
it's honestly a great culture and you
know and everyone has their own
perspective and and differences to it so
I'm I'm so happy to to have Miss Jesse I
now I totally and I got add and I don't
know the last name
again canoer canoer is that
it canoer canoer I got it so so
folks
welcome to the hustle Zone Jesse Connor
no
joking don't you do that
again oh my goodness I knew you were
gonna do that I knew it hey guys canoer
canoer I got it right how are you
doing I am doing great how are you doing
I'm doing good I'm doing good oh now I
got to like switch
so so yeah no I'm I'm doing great so
welcome to the hustle Zone and um you
know you were on the hustle Zone when we
first were trying to figure it out you
know and yes we had we had very
interesting conversations uh you shared
the stage with I think I double booked
that day so I had to put uh I had two
people on and we had my friend Chris yes
and he had a dream board and the dream
board was super hilarious because he
wanted to get late and then he wanted uh
you know a million doar and I'm sure
when you get a million dollars you get
laid from everybody but you know the
reality is is that um you had a very
interest what I what I real what I liked
about that episode was that you know I
never seen a your a a dream board that
detailed in my life you like you had it
all and at that time you accomplished a
lot in that dream board like you did a
lot
so I think that's amazing so you know
from from last time I saw you you're
going to have to share with me what
you've accomplished on the dream board
um this time around but um so like how
how has it
been um it has been amazing it's been a
crazy Journey that's for sure so the
first time I was on the hustle Zone um I
think the biggest thing that we
accomplished was paying off my car which
at the time you know um it was one of
those highin interest cars I'm like I am
never going to be able to pay this off
until I'm like 30 sorry my cat's like
crawling all over me um
anyway um anyway I'm like I'm never
going to be able to pay this car off
because at the time um I needed a car
and funds were crazy before I took this
crazy leap of faith and did something
different and then we wound up being
like a a $10,000 car wound up being like
almost 20 something thousand that we
were paying um while not paying that off
um we uh took a family vacation we um
started our own businesses um like other
side businesses uh we paid for Christmas
in cash which was amazing um and then we
started looking to buy a home
whoa and then this year we did we
crossed off the biggest thing on our
dream board and we bought our first
brand new house holy moly yeah that
serious like it was all on your dream
board I remember it so we're going to
have to go back to that episode and
actually like wow so that really
happened yeah um so I had to make a new
one and not even one year it's been less
than a
year
yeah I I I just I see it I write it down
and I have to go after it you know so
like have you always been this goal or
like you know
driven um honestly no no I wasn't when I
was younger I didn't have like goals or
dreams or anything like that but I guess
that was like due to my background and
where I came from and um you know a a
lot of people know my story that follow
me on Facebook you know I um came from
absolutely nothing I grew up in a
rundown trailer park um my parents I
came from very broken home um I'm
literally The Prodigy of addiction and
mental illness and I I thought I was
just going to fail honestly I didn't
have a lot of dreams and things when I
was a kid um I actually got W up being a
high school dropout and a Teen Mom and
uh having my daughter basically kind of
opened my eyes and made me want to do
more I wanted to show her that you know
she can do anything anything that she
sets her mind to she can do it and so
now I have two kids and I'm 24 and
married and you know um I have to show
them that they can do anything they are
watching every move I make you know my
daughter all the time is very involved
in our team and she's like Mom how's the
team doing like you know and see her
herself being a part of our dream board
because she's six my son is only two so
he doesn't really get it but like with
her Crossing those little things off
that she wants for herself and seeing
that we're doing that with her she
absolutely loves it and I have to set
that example wow so so Jesse you didn't
tell me all this stuff last time um I
know um I think last time U I was so
nervous and you know I I don't know I
sharing my story it took me a lot of
courage to actually kind of let people
in and let them know where I came from
and uh my background and things like
that because it was scary it's getting
out there and just being like hey so
look yeah I might look like I have it
all together but if you knew me eight
years ago you'd be like who is this girl
MH so um I am going to ask you the same
question again uh because this is the
hustle Zone and we're the ones the first
ones to be like what's your story you
know it's so funny I just got to cut to
me for one second here everybody in
their dog in their show is like what's
your story and I want to say that I was
one of the people that invented it first
so you guys need to no I'm
joking I love it I love it all I just
you know I just want to say that for
because I have this I don't know if you
can see on my screen Jesse but I have
the widescreen thing and it's just the
toy that I like to play with sometimes
but it never really
comes it's just
a oh my God this is the hustle Zone
folks but
anyway but but but anyway um so I want
to I want to ask you again you know this
time because now that you've you've
you've opened up to everybody I would
like to know like what is your
story oh my goodness okay so um I guess
starting from a like far far back so
we're going to go 24 years ago actually
it's really funny um I just had this
conversation earlier today with my
father um as he told me I was a backseat
baby of a car that kind of looked like a
Porsche I wasn't supposed to happen but
I happen
um it was jokingly as he said that just
so you guys know okay um so my parents
they were very toxic together they
didn't last long um my mother um she
struggled with a lot of personal issues
when I was growing up and um you
know her story I'm not fully out there
with so I'm not going to go into every
detail but
um my father and I um we've had a rocky
relationship my whole life he's been
kind of in and out um he's very awesome
about me like sharing his story very
openly because if you knew him now he's
like the most awesome person but my
father had a very rough childhood as
well and he grew up um thinking that
drugs and things
were okay um he was dealing and using
and he wasn't very active in my life
when I was growing
up and um spent a lot of time in prison
and I had major major I guess what you
would call Daddy Issues growing up I
rebelled so much I was in trouble kicked
out of school um got sent away I mean I
just I I don't know what I was looking
for in my teen years but um it it
definitely made me who I am now so going
back just a little bit more
um I literally grew up in a rundown
trailer this trailer had holes all over
the walls um it was in this trailer park
um actually I remember this time one of
my friends her parents came to bring her
to my home
and they said that she couldn't stay
because of where I lived it wasn't um a
really good place there were a lot of
drugs actually there was a meth lab that
blew up like two trailers above
me um but I grew up around that stuff I
um didn't really know any better um I
was kind of it was kind of always there
and around in my family so you know I
was like oh it's okay you know and other
people are like what this girl is crazy
but no okay um get a little sidetracked
here so anyways going through through um
school and everything else um I wound up
dropping out of school
because I I couldn't do it I hated going
to school I um was bullied a lot um I
didn't have a lot of friends growing up
um you I was poor um when
my parents were separated my father was
mostly in prison and my mother um you
know she was struggling with her own
stuff and she I had give her credit you
know she she tried she tried but uh you
know she she couldn't do it
um and my grandparents had a huge hand
in raising me and my
siblings and my grandmother is
a um paranoid schizophrenic so if you
know what that is and if you know
anything about schizophrenia it is a
chemical imbalance of the brain and my
grandmother um is was very scary you
know being a young kid you you think you
know your grandma's right because that's
your grandma and you love her so much
and you know she you know would think
that like people were out to get her and
things like that so growing up with that
and just watching her um you know going
through these episodes and um these
things happening to her that weren't
really happening that was so confusing
as a small child
um so that's kind of a little bit of my
background and I got older I
just wanted to Rebel ran away you know
got in trouble with the law uh wound up
meeting my husband at 16 and he kind of
had a little change in my heart I guess
and I um W up getting pregnant and my
daughter pretty much saved my life and
made everything amazing so that's kind
of my story I feel like I was all over
the place with it no no I'm just
listening because I mean like everyone
has a story and I think that um and then
and a story doesn't you know it's not
just uh so I woke up today and I went to
the store and then the end you know like
there's a lot of Side Stories and things
that are happening but you know there's
a few things that I want to kind of
touch on but you know the the like
schizophrenia is no joke and I mean you
know it's just a
symptom of um it's just like
schizophrenia is a symptom that just
like me having an asthma attack when
someone is having an episode and you
know that's just you know it can it
definitely can be managed right so it's
not like people with schizophrenia are
monsters um however you know it is a
challenge sometimes you know dealing
with some people uh with schizophrenia
because they there there is the paranoia
and there's the after effects it's you
know the insecurity and and whatnot so
you know that and even then this was
this was 10 years ago and um back then
you know the medications weren't as
great as they are now because my uncle's
ALS Al a he has severe schizophrenic he
is a severe
schizophrenic um like the medicines
aren't like they were now so it was
trial and error trying to um you know
help balance her out
and you know we all know how medications
go sometimes it works sometimes it
doesn't yeah yeah yeah yeah and how did
you like you being young because you
know when you're a kid you don't really
get it you know you you just see it
happening so when did it start affecting
you um mentally like when did it just
Dawn on you that whoa like this is real
and this is something
different actually I remember this day
very very clearly I was about 9 years
old and I had walked over to my
neighbors um their names I'll just say
Robin and I knocked on their door and I
asked them to stop hurting hurting my
grandma and they sat me down on their
swing and they told me that they weren't
doing anything they they weren't you
know um shocking her or things that she
had thought that they were doing um and
that she was very sick and I think
that's when it kind of hit me
um I guess trying to deal with that
reality that you know maybe the things
that she's saying isn't real but at the
same time she was my grandma
so I you know I loved her and I had her
back and I was like no like this isn't
real cuz I didn't want to believe it but
I knew you know I knew something wasn't
right but at the same time um because of
that in that incident too um growing up
I never
really spoke out anymore you know after
that CU I felt like I tried to go over
there and like be a badass and like
saved my grandma because I love her and
she's like my mom and and I go over
there and they basically like shut me
down you know and so after that I kind
of
just I didn't have like the courage to
like say anything else any other
time and
um did you when did you realize
that you know like being in that situ
being in a broke like you said a broken
home I'm just quoting you um yeah
when like did you ever have any hopes of
you know of being someone someday and
you know being rich and being you know
like did you ever
dream during those times where were like
like were the reality is a little bit
different for you did you not think that
any of that could could
happen um I'm going to be completely
honest no
I honestly I
it's terrible to say but I battle really
bad depression um in my teen years and I
wanted I wanted my life to be over as a
teenager and and that doesn't sound
right right you know especially anybody
that knows me now I'm like a happy fun
bubbly person but back then you know I
had to grow up way too fast and my
childhood was basically ripped away from
me I didn't get to experience all the
cool things that other kids are supposed
to um
because of the fact that I had to grow
up way too fast at a very young
age yeah and um you know and like I
don't have similar I don't have a
similar story but like there are some
parallels um you know just having to
grow up young because my mom was a
single mom and
um and you know she wasn't really around
so we had to teach ourselves how to cook
and stuff like that so I was always
mature than than the other kids and
didn't really get a chance to to uh you
know really enjoy my childhood you know
so to say so you know and and it kind of
when you think about that kind of stuff
it to parents sometimes it doesn't
really matter to kids CU like you know
what kids will forget kids will get over
it but then you know when you get older
and you start raising like what dawned
on me is when I started raising my son
and
realizing you know replaying my life
through my son I started getting
flashbacks memories did that ever happen
when you were raising your
daughter um yeah actually um so many
it's really funny because after we had
um our daughter probably which she is
like two years old we had moved back to
my hometown um which was crazy because I
never in a million years thought I would
move back there and like we would be
driving and I would I I wanted I want to
share a little bit of my life with my
daughter but not yet you know not like
any of the crazy stuff until she's older
and you know things like that of course
but like taking her to um this place
this park where I used to kind of live
by um in that crappy
trailer um flashbacks all the time
and none of them were ever really good
so and now moving forward when was it
the time um
that you realize that hey I got some
hope like you know like my life has
changed and um you know or not my life
has changed but like I'm I'm about to to
venture into something different like
when when did that
happen um honestly when I peed on a
stick and it came back
positive that is when it kind of changed
for me um I never before I and I didn't
want to be a parent I didn't want a
family um because I was like if if I
have a family I'm going to be I'm going
to repeat you know I don't want to be
like my parents D and I think when I
peed on that stick I made a promise to
myself that I was going to do absolutely
everything that I could to be the best
mom that I could be I'm not perfect I'm
not perfect my daughter will tell you
that I'm not perfect but I love my kids
and they have you know everything that
they could possibly want or need you
know I do the best that I can and you
know they don't they don't go without
they
don't they don't live in a a broken
environment either right right I mean
and none of us like none of us are
perfect like today I forgot uh normally
every Friday my son gets a half day and
I forgot to pick him up so I'm like oh
Lord you know and then you you realize
that um you know because for me it's
devastating it's devastating when
whenever I make a mistake but you know
um but then you have to realize that
you're you're parent you know and all
parents make mistakes not every parent
is good but the one thing that with all
parents that you can't replace is the
love that you have for your children you
know it's like I tell my son no one's
going to love
you more than me and my you you know
what I mean no one you know and that
having that telling him that I realized
my mom loves me you know and and my dad
loves me even though I didn't think that
they were perfect either but they love
me because like you know you like they
were holding me in their arms and
everything it's not like I you know I
was a you know like a Manchild when I
was right but the reality is is that
like you know we're not perfect and but
the the fact that your your kids get to
see
you just work is hard but then you
accomplishing your goals I mean that's
going to change their lives
forever you know like they're not going
to go through the same thing watching
their moms like accomplish everything
increment by increment and so when you
had when you had your kid what was the
first decision that you made um to put
your life in a
direction um get a
job that was my first thing was getting
a job I bought this this crappy oh my
goodness this crappy $800 car off
Craigslist um it had no power
steering uh the gas gauge didn't work so
we were always running out of gas
um it oh it had so many issues but I
bought it and it was my car and that's
how I was going to get around and d d
and I was going to go back and forth to
work and you know take my daughter to
her doctor's appointments and everything
like that so I was I was really proud of
that car wow I it's always nice to have
a car right instead of having to take a
bus so you're working you got a car you
met your husband when did you and your
husband decide that you wanted to be
entrepreneurs this is crazy so um
actually it's been two years that we
decided we were going to be
entrepreneurs um we started with Opening
Our Own um Custom Fabrication Shop
canoer Custom Fabrication we do all
kinds of um metal work we make headache
racks we make roll bars we make fire
pits you know everything uh and people
bring us these crazy ideas and my
husband's like Yay let's do it you know
um so we started that two years ago um
at our well my in-laws his parents um
shop and it's it's been overtime it's
been awesome it's been exciting it's
been and fun you know it has its slow
moments things like that but they say
the first three years in business is the
hardest um and then shortly after that I
started my own photography
business and um it was doing great I
loved it I loved it I loved it but my
passion slowly kind of drifted away and
then I kind of got wrapped up in this
crazy Health and Wellness
and I fell in love with it and I just
ran with it and I've never been happier
like I have an awesome team I love what
I do I have amazing clients like it's
it's bomb wow it's the bomb.com and yes
um so when did you who who who gave the
idea to do the dream board the dream
board um well that was kind of just a
thing like I don't know people were
always talking about writing down your
goals and da d and the dream board just
happened like it just out of the blue
happened we started doing it um two
years ago and it was small like a little
bitty board and then it just kind of
grew bigger now we have a smaller one
it's on the fridge but it's like it has
so many more things on it than the other
one
did that's amazing and you know like how
long have you had this dream board in
how long did it take for you to
accomplish all this stuff on
there um so the first one we had for
um like six months and it was like house
first no oh yeah he's over here
dictating my story my husband go put a
shirt
on okay anyways um so the first one um
we had for like six months and then we
crossed it all off and we we were we
were actually at the time we bought our
house and we were moving and it got
ruined so we're like oh we're just going
to make a new one and then so we made
this one that we have now on the fridge
um will you actually bring it to me
bring me the dream board yeah and we um
have started already Crossing things off
on this one which we're super super
excited about um like I said this one's
not as fancy as my other big one but it
works you know it works it's fine so as
soon as he brings it over
here I
stick okay so like I said it's not as
big but there do you remember my my
other one I had on here yeah yeah yeah
yeah it has way more things on it um so
we couple things that we've already
crossed off because D so we put buy our
home back on here because of the fact
that when we moved in here or getting
ready to move we didn't officially buy
it yet so we had it back on this one
when our other one got ruined so we
crossed off buying our home and we have
a beautiful brand new house that was
just built in January and we absolutely
love it and it's so fun wow still smells
new um the next thing was uh we bought a
new
Harley-Davidson
whoa that was that was definitely Kyle's
thing
um this one we're about to cross off and
it's putting a patio out back which we
are going to be doing that in the next
couple weeks like a big big patio to
hang out and have barbecues and family
get togethers and everything 18 by 30
maybe 18 by 30 so we're pretty excited
about
that and then so those are the ones that
we've crossed off already for this year
so I'm going to go ahead and just give
you the rundown of what else we're going
to do this year you ready yep all right
so we're going to finish our basement we
are do a family vacation we're going to
be doing a huge give back um I'm not
100% sure what I want to do this year
but I want to do something big like
maybe like a book drive or something
something like I can do in my community
or maybe like a shoe Drive something fun
um paying off our truck can't wait for
that one uh
skydiving um our trip to Colorado MH um
we want to adopt a family for
Christmas putting in our
fence the kids really really want a big
big pool so that is our that's one
that's on there for them they want that
one so badly um Disneyland of course
because my kids want to go to Disney
we're in the process of planning to take
that trip so I'm super excited um um let
me see I think that's pretty much
everything that I have on here oh and
then of course expanding canoyer custom
um even more um instead of just being
local make it kind of like maybe
Missouri
Statewide
wow that's awesome so I think that um I
think that that like it makes me excited
and and I know that you you said you
were GNA put another uh uh item on that
dream board you were going to pay off
Ryan's debts and
uh yeah
yeah pay off his debt and buy him a new
home and stuff because you got that oh
yeah yeah that's exactly I'll get that
on there
own but um when it when it came to um
you're accomplishing all these
goals do people look at you now and
think you had it all from the beginning
like did people think that you that you
were
lucky yes I cannot I've had messages
like um when I share my story sometimes
on Facebook or I love going live and
sharing things with um all my friends I
I love people like that's what I do I
just love people um and I love sharing
my story but um yeah I've gotten
messages so many times people being like
I would never think that you would be
going through that or people people
think that I have a perfect life and I'm
like what what or um one of the things
one time was H somebody I shared my
story just like you know just some small
little paragraph and an old photo or
whatever and somebody had messaged me
and they're like I would never Peggy for
somebody to go through all that stuff
and I'm like I don't even know what that
means like so because of like where I'm
at right now in life that doesn't mean
that I didn't have any hardships or I
didn't go through things or I haven't
been through hell and backed and fought
my way out you
know and you know and and some people
even for me I can I can I can I can say
the same thing it's like you know um
people just don't know and I don't it's
not that I don't want them to know I was
like Hey I was a bad kid when I was a
teenager and I wanted to see all that
but I think that you know the reality is
is that people have this misconception
about success it's like success is for
those who are lucky and you have to be
Lu lucky and I don't I don't I think
that's like I I I feel like you know um
I feel like success is more so like a
Rubik's Cube if you don't have
the um I think I got Frozen um I think
we're both Frozen oh now we're not
frozen but yeah if you don't have the
algorithm you don't get it you know what
I mean and yes you you just what are
your habits that allow you to get there
like what you know what's your algorithm
success okay so honestly I'm huge huge
huge huge on self-development like I
kind of push it on my team a little bit
but I'm huge um I truly believe that
when I wake up in the morning the first
20 minutes of my day or that's what
matters the most that is how the rest of
my day is going to be so when I wake up
I'm not kidding I turn over I hit my TV
on and I put on um it kind of depends on
who I'm in the mood for but I'm going to
just throw Les Brown out there cuz he's
is amazing um I listen to that and then
you know I I'm listening I'm feeling
them I'm brushing my teeth I'm looking
in the mirror and my team knows I do
this and it sounds crazy but like I will
put my like finger on the mirror be like
you are enough like every single morning
and I know my team thinks I'm crazy
because I do that and I like write
little messages and stuff the night
before on my mirrors um you know I know
that sounds crazy but it's not I promise
it like Works um but like I sit there
and brush my teeth and and I look up and
I'm listening
to uh Les Brown on the TV and I look up
and I see you know my message written
there and then I can sit there and I can
look in the mirror and when I look in
the mirror that that reflection
like when you can actually look in the
mirror and just be like yes like you are
enough you are awesome you know that is
a good feeling because I remember a
point in time in my life that I couldn't
even look in the mirror because I was
just I I was ashamed I I couldn't look
in the mirror and be like oh yeah you
you know um so like I guess my regimen
basically is all about self-development
because every single day I have to grow
as a person in order to help myself help
my family help my team um help people
around me I can't help anybody if I
can't help
myself and um oh I see keep on pressing
the wrong button here I'm going to cut
just to me for a second we're just going
to do a little break um folks I know
that it says Jesse uh canoer the host of
The Hustle Zone that wasn't that was by
accident
so I forgot we cuz I called her like um
probably 8:00 and I said hey do you want
to be on the hone and then we're
scrambling to get everything together
but you know I'm not perfect by any
means but my camera's perfect
y'all perfect and the microphone is
perfect too and the new lens that I got
was perfect so I still got some time to
like screw up a few times I'm joking I
don't um so I apologize um so uh we just
got the tally in and Mark elk Hill won
the1 th000 credit to Bak
creative so Mark you can use that credit
towards uh website or to towards
branding so you know hit me up we'll
have to schedule a time in the next
couple of weeks to go over you know um
in detail you know what you would like
to do with that credit um but
congratulations we had we had a trivia
and the trivia was pretty awesome and
we're going to be doing that like it was
just fun like it it just it's nice to
see the group of people so we're just
going to read the comments we had we had
like a very we had a historic comic come
in through uh the hustle Zone your dad
said you know he's like you know this is
my daughter I'm like whoa that's pretty
powerful you know he's like I cannot
believe it he said something like that
so I'm going to pull up these comments
right now okay oh no I'm not on the
right comment section here let
me there's all these
buttons it's really hard for someone
with dyslexia to like do stuff it's just
like I swear to I I'm dyslexic I
understand I'm always screwing stuff up
okay
but um here okay we we brought in the
comments didn't we and the comments are
not coming through let me just
refresh oh you know what because we
timed out uh times out after an hour so
I can't bring the comments in so what
I'm going to do is I'm just going to
read from what I see and um you know so
you got Lindsay um um
hetrick and she says you are are such an
inspiration and marjerie says girly I
love your
personality okay that's awesome um Billy
Russell says I have an extra dealer he
turned his life around and put my kids
through a lot of pain wow uh my father
that is my father actually Billy Russell
commenting um so he got his GED in
present so he is not the best speller
but what he's trying to say is I have an
I am an ex-drug dealer who turned his
life around and put my kids through hell
oh
wow but look my um I've actually shared
my father's testimony because a lot of
people don't know this but um my father
and I actually just reconnected in the
last
year we're actually have become really
good friends we actually have a really
cool Bond um my kids have even started
calling him POA which is really awesome
uh we hang out pretty much every Sunday
which is really cool he comes over we
barbecue um we have an amazing
relationship now but it hasn't been that
way um it's been the last year yeah I
was 23 when we reconnected I'm 24 um and
he's he um goes to church all the time
and he's turned his whole life around
and he has a really good job and he's
getting married and we love Heather she
is amazing and um he he is an awesome
person now and it's really nice to like
see that and have him a part of of my
life now because I I went so many years
without it and he you know it's awesome
he I've shared his testimony so many
times on my Facebook um you know he he
knows what he did you know he knows that
it was hard it was hard to grow up um or
when I was younger it was seeing them in
glass you know um and then after a while
there was no more visitations and then
when he was home he wasn't being a dad
he wanted
to hustle other things yeah yeah yeah it
was just didn't it didn't click in at
that time you know and oh it's fine yeah
but now you guys have a beautiful
relationship I'm loving the fact that
he's participating in the hustle Zone
this is all live um which is pretty cool
but it really helps me understand you
better because last time when you came
on like you know I just thought oh
she's just regular regular life she is
everything cool I was going to you know
I didn't expect that this was going to
happen today cuz we you know CU you said
no I didn't everything is cool but the
you know the but anyway like I think
this is amazing and you are you are an
inspiration we're going to have to close
this out uh because it's already an hour
holy cow and and I am so long- winded
that I'm so long winded that I uh you
know sometimes the hustle Zone ends at
11:00 and my clients are like when's
that website is it done yet
so um okay
so let's change the line of questioning
here um what's your favorite
movie my favorite what sorry I couldn't
hear you for a second movie okay so my
absolute favorite movie right now is a
dog's purpose like I watched it like 50
times and I cried and it is so good it
is like the sweetest movie ever I had
this dog when I was a kid and he was
like my best friend and he played soccer
and like I love
dogs that's awesome and what is your
favorite dessert favorite dessert
pineapple
cheesecake pineapple cheesecake I've
pineapple cheesecake that sounds so good
it is um it is heaven in your
mouth that's awesome so pineapple
cheesecake and what what pisses you off
what pisses me
off my husband get my videos my husband
I'm just
kidding she's not
kidding anyway um I don't um geez what
really pisses me off um
I do not like judgmental people like I
hate when people feel like they have to
have an opinion of people all the time
like I I don't like that that is like
the one thing that I really get angry
about like I hate when people mom bash I
hate when people when girls are just
absolutely mean to other girls I see it
all the time and I'm just like block and
delete like I can't I can't I hate I
want to say something but I'm just like
oh no I don't like people just being
mean for no reason
okay I'm done okay well that was
interest no I'm
joking I'm going to judge you right now
but um okay and
then if you could turn back the hand of
time what would you say to that young
girl that was growing
up oh my
gosh there's so much I would say say to
her I would say
that it's going to be okay you're going
to get through
it no matter what anybody says you are
absolutely
beautiful
wow wow wow I'm gonna cry right now you
g make me cry right
now oh my gosh wow
uh yeah does that make you feel to say
that it feels
good it's not it's it's crazy I honestly
I've never been asked that question
before so it kind of hits home a little
bit
um but it feels good it feels good to
know that I've come this far yeah it
honestly feels good to see you come this
far and it it it's like anyone if they
apply themselves you know they could
they can be somebody and you've really
demonstrated that and um so let us know
where where we can find
you um absolutely anywhere I am all over
Facebook all over Facebook so go ahead
and add me um I have Instagram and it's
catching up with Jesse Snapchat catching
up with Jesse that's kind of my thing
because um I like to I like to keep life
going and so people just got to play
ketchup with me you know every day is a
new day hey I don't live for yesterday
anymore so catch it up with Jesse so and
will you come back on well I was gonna
ask you you're gonna be a writer for the
hustle zone or do you have time of
course I I love the hustle Zone even
from the first time I was on here and I
was like so nervous and like I didn't
know what to say h yes absolutely I
would write for the hust Zone well I'm
going to send you an email it is very
daunting there's a lot of there's
paperwork and all that stuff but we we
are going to do something really oh yeah
it's uh it's huge okay but it's huge I
really want to have you because I think
your story is amazing and I think that
also um you know even if you didn't tell
the story tonight you know I've been
watching your stuff um like I don't
really get chance to comment or go in to
everybody's like videos right because
like if I did that like I'm sure I would
be like doing the hustles on from like a
bridge somewhere right right but the
um you know but you you just you you
live such a really good life you you
seem really happy and you have a lot of
fun with your lives you're dancing you
got kids and there's just all these
great things so it's it's like you know
folks that's why like this whole 5,000
friend thing like I got 5,000 friends
now and they're all entrepreneurs you
got to keep like folks you got to keep
on adding entrepreneurs because the
thing about it is that you're never
going to find a negative story on your
timeline straight up like every time you
go down unless someone's like blow man
those black lives matter so block and
delete I'm
joking oh gosh without a little bit of
humor but no I but but I rarely see
people being political it is just it's
like LinkedIn but where all the people
are at LinkedIn I find that LinkedIn is
like the place where people think
they're social media in they're
like and then just put it out there and
nothing happens but Facebook is like a
place where you know we all get to see
each other's lives and we all get to see
each other expand and grow and to do
great things and you are one of those
people that's why I remember your name
now and I'll continue to remember your
name
Jen I'm gonna kick your butt Ryan
but thank thank you uh Jesse from the
bottom of my heart thank you for sharing
your story tonight and um absolutely um
there is a tradition on the hustle
Zone where I do a call and response and
then you have to wake up the family and
everything everybody in there and you
got to scream it loud and proud but uh
so I'm going to say welcome to the and
then you're going to be like h
still doing that yeah I you know what I
I'm putting together a video where it's
going to be like hustle and then we're
going to have all the people like oh so
it's going to be commercial for the
magazine
so all right it's gonna be huge but
anyway so welcome to
the hustle zound oh I love it I love it
thank you so much so um thank you I'm
just going to break to me so folks we
could not do this without so when you
guys see let me know when you guys see
the the comment section on the top when
it goes or it disappears let me know um
because that means I got to wrap it up
um because I think Facebook only allows
you to have access to a key for a
certain period of time but I also need
to get going because I Can Do the Hustle
Zone all day every day um again hustle
own shirts I don't think we are selling
this hustle own shirt um but I I
probably want the it to be all gold
Philip Woods if you're talk if you're
hearing us um but uh you know please
purchase a hustle Zone shirt keep the
hope alive you know the hustle Zone um
we are actually donating
$10,000 worth of credit towards a um to
a school that is being built in
California so that is going to be um uh
we're going to give them a full
marketing package a full uh website and
all that good stuff a courtesy of hustle
Zone and bowai creative because we
really love to build the communities and
and you know this is this is a group
this is a this is a school that is built
around
entrepreneurialism so it's a business
school for kids and I think that's just
amazing so of course I had to put my
dollars and cents in and um you know put
my money where my mouth is and that's
what we're doing so um either way folks
uh I love you guys from the bottom of my
heart you guys you guys are the reason
why I do this every night at: Mountain
Standard Time and um you know please
check us out hustles
own. purchase a
t-shirt you know
$20 what would you spend those $20 on
nowadays you can't you can buy four
Starbucks coffees for four Starbucks
coffee you can buy yourself
a I wish you know what the next thing on
my dream board that I'm going to put I'm
going to put like sound effects machine
so that I can put like you know some sad
music you know like the sad music that
you would watch on full Full House yeah
that's going to be me it's going to be
like
da you know what anyway I got to go I
digress I gotta I have to uh my son is
itching to get back to his computer that
he has so um I will let you guys go and
congratulations to mark elkhill for you
know winning ,000 credit towards
websites and branding packages thank you
so much folks for tuning in and every
week you're going to start winning stuff
because we're not stopping here um and
if
Jesse canoer
she's looking at me right now she's like
she's squinting she's like you better
not you better stop doing
that hopefully her business can donate
some stuff to the hustle Zone and we'll
give it away um and all the other
businesses out there if you guys want to
donate whatever I will happily give it
away because you know what if you guys
want to think about the hustle the
hustle zones about love unity and
inclusion we have all kinds of people on
here and we don't discriminate we don't
want to hate on people that are starting
the journey we had Susan day was
homeless now she's like you know she's
picking her life up but she's selling
books at $50 a pop and some of the Big
Wigs couldn't even do that so you know
mad love to Susan day and thank you
Susan for doing the tallies for me and I
love you guys hustle on baby so let me
put on those
credits before I go
um and I I you know because it was so
last minute today I didn't put um
Jesse's name so I'm going to put them
into the credits right now so that we
can put this on indb have you guys heard
of IND DB but that's where you go in
when you type in a movie IND DB comes up
and once you're in the once you're in
IMDb you're considered an actress so
Jesse is now considered and Atrix are
you still there Jesse I'm here
I could already tell you had enough um
hold on one second here she's like I'm
here I'm here okay so I'm just putting
your name in the credits right now so
Jesse c c o n o y e r see I spelled it
right can look at you go so we're going
to put that there
and and we're going to put the credits
I feel like a grandpa Jesse like here
let me just break to you for a second
here I honestly feel like I I I'm so I
don't know what it is lately I just feel
so slow and I'm like I'm just going to
just do this right now I'm going to
click on this and hopefully oh no it's
Uh something's wrong with that so yeah
man I've been kind of really slow on
this uh hustle zoning thing
but oh and then she's letting her phone
and I broke to you oh my God okay I'm
going back I digress
so what
happened oh I'm right here okay perfect
so we're going to break to those
credits so there we go so Jesse's in the
credits and uh thank you guys so much
and if you guys want to get on to the
hustle Zone show because you guys don't
want to hear me talk about um stuff all
the time just please hit me up I'll get
you book you into one of the hustle own
shows so thank you guys so much and
thank Our Guest Jesse and yeah and we
are out